we fight to the last Ukrainian, you to the
мы воюем до последнего украинца вы до
last Russian, what do you need,
последнего руска вам что нужно
territories or living people,
территории или живые люди
and this and that, and so on, then stop, stop, why do you need our
и то и то и так то стоп стоп зачем вам
territories, well, they’ll come in
наши территории
handy? And so you
ну пригодятся по А то есть ты
support the seizure of Ukrainian territory,
поддерживаешь захват территории Украины
you support the war against Ukraine, well, rather not, well, rather not,
ты поддерживаешь войну против Украины
the question is,
ну скорее нет ну как скорее нет вопрос
rather not, what’s not clear to you,
ну как скорее нет что тебе непонятного
you supported it a minute ago, clearly,
ты минуту назад поддерживал чётко
hello, zra, hello, I’m from the
здравствуйте зра здравствуйте я из
city of Khmelnitsky, where are you from, Siberia,
города Хмельницкий вы откуда сибирь
Krasnoyarsk, it’s cool, that’s where you have the
Красноярск прикольно это у вас там где
black sky because of coal, yes, yes,
чёрное небо объявляет из-за угля да да
you know, I understand, my father is from
да вы шарите понял у меня отец родом из
Krasnoyarsk, just yes, yes, and my cousins
Красноярска просто да да и двоюродные
live there, and how do you communicate, yes,
там живут а чем общаетесь
whatever you have to, it depends on your interlocutors,
да чём придется от собеседников зависит
people are different, you know, I understand, how do you feel about the fact that
люди разные знаете понял как относитесь
Russia is at war with Ukraine,
к тому что Россия воюет с Украиной
yes, it’s been going on for three years now, no, you
да уже уже третий год идёт нет вы
feel that way, well,
относитесь
I’m explaining that some
ну я же объясняю уже какие-то
emotional
эмоциональные
aspects have already faded away, like, over time,
аспекты сошли на нет типа со временем
everything dulls, and that’s why,
всё притупляется и поэтому
that is, in principle, what
то есть в принципе а какие у вас были
emotional aspects did you have before, before
раньше эмоциональные аспекты до того как
you came, well,
вы прились
at first, in  at the very beginning very
ну поначалу в самом начале очень
negative that is well it's
негативные то есть ну это
some kind of a-a then rather some kind of such
какой-то а-а потом скорее какая-то такое
negative such a
негативное такое вот
tonic feeling you know such a
чувство тоническое такое знаете такой
negative
негатив
then like well it
потом типа
turned out that after all some
ну оказалось что всё-таки какие-то
conclusions were made and not everything is as
выводы были сделаны и не всё
if but in general well I don't know
так как будто бы но в целом ну не знаю
everything is bad but come what may as they
всё плохо но уже будь что будет как
say
говорится
and you have some other not I'm
а у вас есть другой какой-то не мне
just interested in how it happens well
просто интересно как типа происходит ну
among Russians the evolution of thought and how do you
у россиян эволюция мысли а как вот вы
think how many Russians have already died in
считаете сколько уже россиян погибло на
this war I
этой войне
don't know 1,100 probably
не знаю 1.100 наверное
what for you 1,100 Russians killed is
что для вас 1.100 россиян погибших это
not enough a lot
мало много
and what do we compare
а с чем мы сравниваем
with your feelings how do you think
с вашими ощущениями как вы считаете
with my feelings well my feelings do
с моими ощущениями ну мои ощущения никак
not correlate or are not connected with the
не колирует или не взаимосвязано со
deaths of
смертьями
Russians yeah for me one
россиян угу для меня один много
understood a lot how do you think how many more
понял как вы считаете сколько ещё должно
Russians should die so that Russian
погибнуть россиян чтобы российское
society understands
общество поняло
that this war is not needed well
что не нужна эта война
listen this is a very
ну слушайте это очень такой
emotional question about nothing and
эмоциональный вопрос ни о чём а
specific actions you will propose for
конкретные действия вы предложите
example what to do let's say for a
например вот что сделать допустим
Russian for example to me no no I'm not
россиянину например мне нене я же не
saying what to do  I mean that
говорю что делать я вот имею в виду что
while many of you Russians
пока вот у вас многие россияне
support, I understand, support the war,
поддерживают поняла поддерживают войну
how many Russians do you think need to
как вы считаете что сколько нужно чтобы
die so that other
погибло россиян чтобы уже другие
Russians will say: "No, this war is
россияне говорили: "Нет этой войны уже
no longer necessary?"
не нужно?"
Well, this is the essence of war, you may not
Ну в этом и суть войны вы может не
understand, but the essence of war is that
понимаете но суть войны в том что
some people close to you die and you
погибают какие-то люди близкие тебе и ты
avenge them and for you the war is justified, that
мстишь и для тебя война оправдана то
is, conditionally, and the war may have been started by
есть условно а война может быть начата
your side
твоей стороной
unfairly, but when your
несправедливо но когда умирают твои
brothers die, you avenge them and for
братушки ты за них мстишь и как бы для
you it becomes fair, that is,
тебя становится справедливо то есть
war is not about justice, it is a
война - это не про справедливость это
cruel fra, my people, I did not ask about
жестокая фра свои я же не спросил про
justice, well, look, before,
справедливость ну смотри вот раньше
many Russians supported everything there, take
много россиян поддерживали там всё взять
Kyiv and so on, and now they see that there are
Киев и так дальше да сейчас смотрят что
still more and more dead
всё-таки больше и больше погибших
Russians and fewer and fewer, then people
россиян да и меньше и меньше тогда людей
think that why this war, well, it
думают что а зачем эта война ну
supports the war,
поддерживает войну как вы считаете
how many Russians do you think should die? 200,000
сколько должно погибнуть россиян 200.000
million, yes, so that all Russians, the
миллион да чтобы уже все россияне
majority, would say: "No, this war is not
большинство говорило: "Нет этой войны не
necessary." Let's make your question more specific,
нужно" давайте конкретизируем ваш вопрос
let's ask it this way. What is the best way to stop
давайте так спросим как лучше остановить
this war? I would probably stop it along the
эту войну наверное я бы остановил по
current front line. If it
линии фронта текущею вот если бы она
were frozen now, look, no,
была заморожена сейчас смотрите нет
look, you and I cannot
смотри мы с вами ничего не это не можем
stop anything. Yes.  neither you nor I but we can
остановить да ни я ни вы но мы можем
say: "I support the war or I do not
говорить: "Я поддерживаю войну или я не
support the war" yes, you as
поддерживаю войну" да вот вы как
Russians yes, that's good if you
россияне да вот хорошо если так вы
describe the question like this: "I do not support the
вопрос обрисовываете: "Я не поддерживаю
war but I support Russia" my
войну но я поддерживаю Россию" моя
country may be wrong but it is my
страна может быть не права но это моя
country yeah, I get it I
страна угу
wonder if it doesn't seem to you that
понял интересно а не кажется ли вам что
during Nazi Germany
во время нацистской Германии также
some Germans also thought yeah, I may not
некоторые немцы мыслили да я может не
think it's wrong there that Hitler was in the
считаю неправильно там что Гитлер в
gas chambers yeah, but I support my
газовых камерах да но я поддерживаю свою
country that would be wrong I agree
страну это будет неправильно согласен
if your country now decides, for example, to
если ваша страна сейчас примет например
drop a nuclear bomb on Moldova for example,
скинуть ядерную бомбу например на
you will support it because
Молдову вы будете поддерживать потому
it is simply your country no no I
что это просто ваша страна
will not support it but it is an irrational decision of course I will not support no so so why do you support it well what are
буду поддерживать нет так так а почему
my options there are options
ну а какие у меня варианты есть варианты
not to support
не поддерживать
well what to do well just don't
ну и что сделать ну просто не
support and why do you
поддерживать а зачем вот вы
support it just well what do I
поддерживаете просто ну что я
support my country why
поддерживаю свою страну зачем
because it is my country I think that
потому что это моя страна я считаю что
being a cosmopolitan is not good no well
быть космополитом - это нехорошо не ну
look let's do it this way you do you support your father
смотрите давайте так вы вы своего отца
because he is your father
поддерживаете потому что он ваш отец
yeah of course yeah if your father takes a
да конечно да если ваш отец возьмёт
knife and cuts the throats of all your neighbors  just
ножик и будет горло всем соседям просто
walk will you support him in this
ходить вы будете его поддерживать в этом
simply because he is your neighbor no no oh
просто потому что он ваш сосед нет нет о
that is you see
то есть видите
support of parents support of the motherland it is
поддержка родителей поддержка родины она
not absolute it still depends on what the
не абсолютная она всё-таки зависит от
Motherland does yes or do
того что Родина делает да или считаете
you think it is right or wrong of
вы это правильным или неправильным
course so that means if you
конечно так то значит если вы
support Russia in the war against
поддерживаете Россию в войне против
Ukraine it means you support this
Украины значит вы поддерживаете эту
war
войну
no
нет
explain well
объясните
what is clear to me I think that this
ну что мне понятно я считаю что эта
war is wrong in every sense
война неправильная во всех смыслах
but I support the whole country I just don't see then it
но я поддерживаю всю страну просто я не
turns out look then it
вижу тогда получается смотрите тогда
turns out Let's be interesting
получается Давайте давайте интересно
just look I don't see any alternatives to
просто смотрите я не вижу альтернатив
getting out of this war that is let's say conditionally
выхода из этой войны то есть условно
retreat at the border in ninety-
допустим отступить на границе девяносто
one what will be the advantages for
первого года какие будут плюсы для
Russia only disadvantages
России только минусы
and complete in Russia will begin
и полнейший в России начнётся
we say support or support just the
мы говорим поддержи или поддержи просто
current so that people don't die everything just
текущие чтобы люди не умирали всё просто
look then it turns out when your father
смотри тогда получается когда отец твой
yes cuts the neighbors yes runs around drunk yes and
да режет соседям да бегает пьяный да и
you say like yes I don't support but
ты говоришь типа да я не поддерживаю но
dad doesn't need to stop either now
остановиться бате тоже не нужно сейчас
yes because in short and return to his
да потому что короче и вернуться в свой
house yes because now the cops will come and
дом да потому что сейчас приедут менты и
will ask witnesses and it's better for him to
будут ээ свидетелей спрашивать а лучше
in short have a needle
пусть он короче иглу
let him be the best player
пусть он лучший игрок
it turns out
так получается
not I just didn't understand they will be killed
не я просто не понял их грохнет
and they will be killed I understood everything
а их грохнет всё понял
no why will I try in this situation
нет почему я попытаюсь в данной ситуации
I will try to stop my father if
я попытаюсь останить отца если зависит
it depends on the circumstances conditionally if these are,
от обстоятельст условно если это
let's say, extremely
допустим люди максимально
marginal people who are worth little,
маргинальные люди которые ну мало чего
well, I don't know, there are local
стоят ну не знаю там местные
killers there and he is drunk because they are, let's say,
убийцы и он их попьяне потому что они на
well, I will try to stop him
допустим ну я попытаюсь его остановить
if he is there I don't know there are innocent children
если он там не знаю там невинных детей
then my father's safety will become
то тогда безопасность моего отца станет
secondary because well, after all,
на второй план потому что ну всё-таки
it's super yeah look different
это де супер да смотри разные
circumstances influence really super a
обстоятельства влияют на реально супер
couple of days ago your father that
пару дней пару дней назад ваш отец то
is your country Russia killed innocent
есть ваша страна Россия убила невинных
children in the city of Krivoy Rog in residential
детей в городе Кривой Рог в жилых
areas yeah a ballistic missile by the way
кварталах так да баллистическая ракета
how many children were killed how do you
сколько кстати детей убило как вы к
feel about it and
этому относитесь
how many children were killed how do you feel about it I'm
а а сколько детей убило как вы к этому
not really interested I was given different numbers it's
не мне правда интересно мне разные цифры
just that I I'm interested in how you
называли просто я Мне интересно как как
feel about it negatively of course and
относишься к этому негативно конечно а
how can you feel about the murder of children
как можно к убийству детей относиться
it's stupid but you support
это глупость но поддерживаешь
that you support well come on so what's
что поддерживаю хорошо давай так что для
more important for you yes so that Russia remains on the
тебя важнее да чтобы Россия осталась на
demarcation line yes  but
линии разграничения да но продолжали
children continued to die in Ukraine or so that Russia would
умирать дети в Украине или чтобы Россия
leave the occupied territories for its
ушла из оккупированных территорий на
own
свою
land and stop the war
землю да и прекратила войну
well look what if let's say Russia goes to the
ну смотри а если допустим Россия идёт на
border of 1991 let's say
границ девяносто первого года допустим
devastation begins in Russia itself and then
начнётся разруха в самой России и тогда
children will die in Russia do we
будут умирать дети в России мы этих
count these children or they don't count so
детей считаем или они не считаются так
stop stop stop wait again I didn't
стоп стоп стоп ещё раз подожди я не
quite understand that is you are now uh fighting
совсем понял то есть вы сейчас ээ воюете
against Ukraine so that you don't start
против Украины чтобы у вас не началась
devastation I can't understand how what kind of devastation
разруха не могу понять как какая разруха
will begin in Russia if Russia withdraws to the
начнётся в России если Россия отойдёт на
border of 1991 what will
границе девяносто первого года что
happen well there are
случится
a lot of problems that is it turns out a lot of
ну много проблем то есть получается куча
regions will become part of a neighboring
регионов войдут в состав соседнего
state that
государства которое к жителям этих
will not be very loyal to the residents of these regions and what will happen in
регионов будет не очень лояльно а в
Russia what does Russia have to do with it what
России что будет причём тут России какие
problems will there be in Russia well okay well it
проблемы в России будут
seems to me there will be a lot of problems
ну хорошо ну мне кажется много проблем
what well that is to say
будет какие ну
conditionally if tomorrow Vladimir
ну то есть условно если завтра Владимир
Putin decides to withdraw to the border of
Путин принимает решение отойти на границ
1991 that is to say how will this be
девяносто первого года то есть как это
accepted in the army for example that is to say a
будет принято в армии например то есть
lot of people are fighting for their country the question is the
куча людей воюет за свою страну вопрос
question how was it accepted in the army when
вопрос а как было принято в армии когда
uh the decision was made to withdraw from  Kherson
ээ было принято решение уйти из Херсона
that someone in the army was against it they took it and
что кто-то в армии был против взяли и
went out and that's it well
вышли и всё
how many people there were in Kherson at that
ну сколько населения в Херсоне на тот
time what difference did it make look well the
период было какая разница смотри ну
army is Russian and the population of
армия же российская причём население
Kherson doesn't make a difference look five
Херсоня разница не смотри умрёт пять
children will die conditionally yes let's take
детей условно да вот возьмём экстремумы
some extremes five children will die or 10,000 there is a
какие-то умрёт пять детей или 10.000
difference or not probably in
разница есть или разницы нет наверное в
quantity there is a difference this is a very
количестве есть разница это очень
big thing well still
большая вещь ну ещё
quite a big size higher than Kherson
разма довольно большое выше чем Херсона
let's ask the question yes but in Russia
давай так вопрос такой да но в России
look Russia left there Kherson left
смотри Россия вышла из там Херсона вышла
Crimea Donetsk Lugansk and
из Крыма Донецка Луганска да самой
Russia itself nothing will happen from this no
России от этого же ничего не будет ни
rallies or protests everyone
митингов ни протестов все спокойно
will take it calmly and everything won't go so stop that is
воспримут и всё не пог так стоп то есть
you want to say that Russians
ты хочешь сказать что россияне из-за
will go out to a rally for something
чего-то выйдут на митинг
yes of course for what reason are Russians ready to
да конечно из-за чего россияне готовы
go out to a rally when was the last time you
выйти на митинг ты когда последний раз
were at a rally
был на митинге
damn what year wait wait
блин в каком году погоди подождёшь
a minute I'll tell you let me tell you
минутку я тебе скажу давай
now I'll
сейчас
say pu-pu-pu-pupupupu
скажу пу-пу-пу-пупупупупу где-то у
I'll
меня сейчас
rewind some
отмотаю
photos somewhere now in the twenty-second year in February
фоточки в двадцать втором году в феврале
well most likely earlier earlier it's most likely
ну скорее всего раньше раньше это скорее
in Listen not this directly earlier most
в Слушай не это прямо раньше скорее
likely twenty-first year was yeah that
всего двадцать первый год был угу то
is what will happen to a person now
есть что будет с человеком сейчас
who goes to an unauthorized rally
который выйдет на митинг неразрешённый
depends on the circumstances well what do you think
от обстоятельств зависит ну как думаешь
well from
ну от
detention to just for example it won't happen yeah
задержания до просто ни например не
someone can be jailed most of them can
угу кого-то и посадить могут большинство
do that well I went out that is well
так и сделают могут ну я выходил то есть
I went out I wasn't jailed well now yes well
ну я выходил меня не сажали ну сейчас да
now when
ну вот сейчас когда так ужесточили
the legislation of the farm has been tightened so much what do you think for
законодательство фермии как ты думаешь
example if Putin now says: "
например если сейчас Путин говорит: "Мы
For example we are leaving the city of Sudzha that's
например уходим из ээ города Суджа вот
how it was yes Russian troops left the
как было да российские войска вышли из
city of Sudzha did someone in the army protest
города Суджа кто-то в армии протестовал
or did someone in Russia go to a rally?"
или кто-то в России вышел на митинг?"
Was there such a thing, no, there wasn't,
Было такое
but why didn't anyone come out to the
не было а почему никто не вышел на
rally, why did they leave Sudzha,
митинг что почему оставили Суджу
well, again, the context is important, that is, it's
ну опять же контекст важен то есть
obvious that there was a successful Ukrainian
очевидно что было удачное украинское
offensive at that moment, yeah, well, it wasn't just like that, they
наступление в тот момент угу
came out just for fun, like, oh okay, we're surrendering, we're coming out, like, you're capturing, well, like, that didn't
типа ой ладно всё сдаёмся выходим типа
happen, yeah, that
захватываете ну типа такого не было да
is, it's obvious that there was a larger recruitment of
то есть очевидно там был больший набор
Ukrainian troops and that's why they came out, well,
украинских войск и поэтому вышли ну
obviously, the context is important, that is, I understand, I
очевидно же контекст важен то есть Понял
understand, super, super question if they tell you
понял супер супер вопрос если вам скажут
that listen, well, there was a big push by
что слушайте ну вот был большой напор
Ukrainian troops and we went beyond the borders of
украинских войск и мы вышли за границы
1991,
девяносто первого года
well, it seems to me that no one will believe it,
ну мне кажется никто не поверит
but how do you know, you don't have
а откуда вы знаете вы не владеете
intelligence information, and so on, yes, they'll tell you that the
разведой информацией и так дальше да вам
generals saw the
скажут генералы видели
situation, NATO generals were
обстановку натовские генералы тут
bombing here, listen, and they'll tell you the same thing, will
бомбили слушай а вам скажут то же самое
you believe it, well, it's just, well, somehow, okay, let's
вы поверите ну просто ну как-то хорошо
dig deeper into this question,
давай вот глубже копнём этот вопрос
how can we know that the Earth is round,
откуда мы можем знать что Земля круглая
no, that's already ethology, that's
вот нет это это уже этология это
chatter, look, I mean, why is that,
болтология смотри в смысле а почему это
look, the point is that no one in Russia will
смотри суть в том что никто в России не
go against your tsar, no one if
пойдёт против вашего царя никто если
tomorrow the king will say: "We are sending troops to
царь завтра скажет: "Вдим войска в
Afghanistan" you will clap your hands
Афганистан" вы будете хлопать в ладоши
if the king says: "We are withdrawing troops from
если царь скажет: "Выводим войска из
Afghanistan" you will clap your hands well
Афганистана" вы будете хлопать в ладоши
what's wrong well
ну что не так
what difference does it make you have formed your own
ну какая разница ты своё мнение составил
opinion you are not interested in other people's opinions that is,
тебе чужое мнение не интересно то есть
you want to speak out well speak up brother I don't
ты хочешь выговориться ну говори брат я
know just here's a question about
не знаю просто вот вопрос по поводу а
authorities it is important I agree that is, the
авторитетов он важен я согласен то есть
question is the same is the Earth round or not
вопрос тот же вот Земля круглая или нет
I have not been in space you have not been either but we
я в космосе не был ты тоже не был но мы
believe that it is round because we
верим что она круглая потому что мы
trust authority I was in space
доверяем авторитету я был в космосе
when I flew last year
когда летал в прошлом году
last year what is your last name well
в прошлом году как твоя фамилия ну-ка
let's google it with a commercial mission with a
давай загуглим с коммерческой миссией с
commercial mission or Well
коммерческой миссией или
okay well cool I saw it with my own
Ну ладно ну крутой я сам видел своими
eyes you see well everything is fine
глазами видишь ну всё хорошо
then look because you have not seen God you have not seen God
то смотри бо Бога не видел бога не видел
there in space there is no God well you see here's an
там в космосе нет бога нет
interesting question for you
интересный
look it turns out that Russians do not
смотри получается что россияне не
go out to rallies either for raising
выходят на митинги ни за повышение
pensions or for low salaries or for
пенсий ни за низкие зарплаты ни за
sending them  nowhere to the SVO and here when they
отправку их на СВО никуда а тут когда
say: "Damn, let's end all
скажут: "Блин давайте мы закончим всё
this, they will suddenly come out to a rally" who
это они вдруг выйдут на митинг" кто
can describe the portrait of a person who will
можешь описать портрет человека который
come out to a rally, uh, against the withdrawal of troops
выйдет на митинг ээ против вывода войск
from Ukraine, who will it be, a liberal, for
из Украины кто это будет либерал там
example, a pensioner,
например пенсионер
well, so let's estimate, well, first of all, the
ну так на прикидку допустим ну во-первых
army will be
армия будет
against the army - who exactly is it,
против армия - это кто конкретно генерал
some general or a private,
какой-то или рядовой кто
well, our generals are tame plus or minus,
ну генералы у нас ручные плюс-минус у
you are also
вас тоже
tame, so most
ручные так что скорее
likely ordinary soldiers, well, who is a
всего обычные солдаты ну кто
mobilized contract soldier, who will be
мобилизированный контрактник кто будет
against and what will he do,
против и что он сделает
well, probably everyone is like
ну наверное все
everyone else, everyone will just start
как все вот все так возьмут и
talking: "Let's be against" and what will
заговорятся: "Давайте будем проти" и что
they do, well, I do
они сделают
n't know what they will do, it's hard to
ну не знаю что они сделают сложно
predict such things, that is, you say, well, okay, let's say, that is, in
прогнозировать такие вещи то есть ты так
your opinion, it is
ну хорошо допустим то есть по-твоему
possible to make concessions to another country in a
можно пойти на уступки другой стране в
war and not get anything for it, well, for
войне и ничего за это не получить да вот
example, the Soviet withdrawal of troops from
например ээ советский вывод войск из
Afghanistan, when they withdrew troops from
Афганистана когда вывели войска из
Afghanistan, the army was against it,
Афганистана что армия была против
everyone finally sighed, ugh,
все вздохнули наконец-то фу блин
damn, a different nature of war, obviously,
ну другой характер войны очевидно
wait, what kind of nature, it was protracted there for
подожди какой характер затяжно там
ten years, well, it was
десяток лет был
protracted  ten years well that is you do
ну да затяжно десяток лет ну то есть ты
not see the difference between the current war
не видишь различия между текущей войной
and the war and what is the difference what is the difference the
и войной а в чём различие в чём различие
intensity of military actions the
интенсивность у боевых действий
intensity of military actions and
интенсивность боевых действий и
what how does the intensity of military actions
что как интенсивность боевых действий
affect in your opinion yes I ask I
влияет по-твоему да я я спрашиваю я
ask how does it affect that for example
спрашиваю как оно влияет что например
people if they are told: "Look we are
люди если им скажут: "Смотрите мы
ending the war everything is pointless and we are
заканчиваем войну всё она бессмысленна и
leaving"
выходим"
so once again
так ещё раз
uh we are ending what is the question the question
э мы заканчиваем в чём вопрос-то вопрос
again: what is the difference between intensity and
ещё раз: чем отличается интенсивность
non-intensity if in both
неинтенсивность если и в том и в том
cases they say: "We are ending the war and
случае скажут: "Мы заканчиваем войну и
withdrawing the troops" the army sighs and leaves the
выводим войска" армия вздыхает и уходит
army of affairs look the army it just
армия дела смотри армия у неё просто
has an order to do the truth well not
есть приказ делают правда
always yes the order is not discussed the truth well for
ну не всегда да приказ не обсуждается
example such a concept as a
правда ну например такое понятие как
military junta yes in Latin America
военная хунта да в Латинской Америке
military is a common phenomenon in Latin America
военно это частое явление в Латинской
yes that is there the military often
Америке да то есть там часто военные
seized power that's right military
захватывали власть правильно военная
junta I understand correctly it's uh let's say a
хунта я правильно понимаю это э скажем
rebellion of some generals so well the
восстание генералов каких-то так
title I don't know rather a rebellion of the army
ну звание не знаю скорее восстание армии
no not an army and a junta -
нет не армия ихунта -
this is the military leadership when it takes
это это военное руководство когда берёт
power well military is not an army the military
власть да ну военно это не армия военное
leadership is not an army  no, so you
руководство это не армия нет так вот ты
yourself said that all these
же сам говорил что у вас все эти
generals are tame, yes, which of your
генералы ручные да кто из ваших
generals can take power then, uh, and
генералов может взять тогда ээ власть и
what's stopping him from taking power now,
что ему мешает сейчас тогда взять власть
well, now, as it were, there is some kind of common
ну сейчас как бы есть
policy for the country, yes, that
какая-то политика страны общая да то
is, there is a conditionally common enemy and
есть есть там условно общий враг и
so on, against, well, there was a little man, so
прочее против ну был человечек так
to speak, who went on a march to Moscow, but
сказать который пошёл марша в Москву но
what happened, yes, nothing, well, as if he
что получилось да ничего ну как бы он
understood that this would not achieve
понял что добиться этим не удастся
anything, there will be no junta, really,
ничего никакой хунты не будет правда
why does this work in this logic,
почему как это работает в этом логике
like Prigozhin didn't succeed, therefore there will
типа у Пригожна не получилось поэтому
never be any junta, what's the matter? And
никогда никакой хунты не будет причём А
who is who, well, who is such as I'm not
кто кто хорошо кто есть такой как я не
talking about a military junta, that it is
говорю про военную хунту что она
obligatory, like, let's see,
обязательно типа давай посмотрим у
Prigozhin had a resource, yes, he had a
Пригожина был был ресурс да у него
private military company, he had
частная военная компания была был
great authority, yes, can you name
авторитет большой да можешь назвать
someone similar, I do
кого-то аналогичного
n't know, some Surovikin or other now,
не знаю суровикин какой-нибудь сейчас
Syrovikin,
Сыровикин
well, what powers does
ну а какие сейчас полномочия у
Syrovikin have now, who is he anyway, who the hell knows,
Сыровикина кто он вообще да хуй знает
he's been out of business for a long time, okay, well,
вот он давно уже типа не при делах
you asked me to name you, I
о'кей ну ты попросил назвать я тебя
named you, yeah, then look, do I understand correctly
назвал угу то смотри я правильно понимаю
that no civilians will
что из гражданских вообще никто не
come out to
выйдет на
protest against the withdrawal of troops from Ukraine
митинг против вывода войск из Украины
well why maybe they will come out I just Yes a
ну почему возможно выйдет я просто Да
portrait a portrait of someone who will come out
портрет портрет того кто выйдет вот
can you explain who will come out
можешь объяснить кто это выйдет
pensioners students who are the driving force
пенсионеры студенты кто движущая сила
among those who come out there will be both pensioners and
среди вышедших будут и пенсионеры и
students so the question is at least one
студенты так вопрос хотя бы один
pensioner and one student no well we are
пенсионер и один студент не ну мы же
talking about a social portrait it is clear that
говорим социальный портрет ясно что
someone can come out maybe an
кто-то один может выйти может и
American can come out yes you can tell a
американец выйти да можешь сказать
portrait what social group
портрет вот какая социальная группа
will support this protest
будет поддерживать вот этот протест
against the withdrawal of troops from Ukraine well I
против вывода войск из Украины ну я тебе
answered you most likely the army not from
ответил скорее всего армия не не из
civilians I mean something from
гражданских имею в виду я что-то из
civilians yes well
гражданских да
such turbo patriots most likely
ну такие турбопатриоты скорее всего
who think that this is a righteous war
которые считают что это праведная война
yeah in short a limited number of a
угу короче ограниченное количество
small number of people I
небольшое людей я
understand well here maybe maybe not in
понял ну тут может быть может нет на
fact it is difficult to judge in such things that
самом деле сложно судить в таких вещах
is you reason like that you draw
то есть ты так рассуждаешь ты делаешь
conclusions as if this can be judged
выводы как будто об этом можно судить
easily I would just look at it from an
легко просто я бы на это смотрел с
economic point of view conditionally yes that
экономической точки зрения условно да то
is pros and cons debit and credit that
есть плюсы и минусы дебит и кредит то
is conditionally the withdrawal of
есть условно вывод
troops on the border money of the first year what
войск на границ дено первого года что
will Russia give a
даст Россия
stop Stop the hockey stick yes look
остановку Остановку клюшки да смотри
stop the war yes uh the opportunity to
остановка войны да ээ возможность
launch  to spend huge amounts of money not on war
пускать пускать деньги не на войну
but on the development of their territories, their
огромные а на развитие своих территорий
people, and if there is such an opportunity, wait,
своих людей а будет такая возможность
take a bill, what is this, well, look,
погоди счёт взял что такое ну смотри
if now a huge amount of money is
если сейчас огромное количество денег у
spent on missiles that fly across
вас тратится на ракеты которые летят по
Ukraine and the war, and so it will be spent
Украине да и войну а так будет тратиться
on the development of the economy, and so missiles
на развитие экономики а так ракеты
will not be produced, yes, in your opinion, well, not
производить не будут да по-твоему ну не
in such quantities,
в таком количестве
well, let's say there is a risk that Ukraine
ну допустим если будет риск что Украина
will enter the Kursk region again, there Sudzhe,
войдёт в Курскую область снова там судже
the long-suffering one, again, they will
многострадальная снова вот
conduct missiles again, you
проведут ракеты снова понадобятся ты ты
understand, yes, what if Russia goes beyond the
ж понимаешь да что если Россия выйдет за
borders of 1991, yes,
границы девяносто первого года да вот
after that, if Ukraine even a meter
после этого если Украина хоть на метр
sticks its nose into Russian soil, this is for the
сунется на российскую землю это для
whole world, Ukraine will be an aggressor, everyone will
всего мира Украина будет агрессор от неё
abandon it, really,
откажутся все правда
why, well, because it will be that it
почему ну потому что будет что она
attacked,
напала
well, and in court, it also attacked, what's not, in
так а ну а в суд же тоже напала в чём
Sudzhe it is defending itself because
нет в судже она защищается потому что
Russia attacked, and if Russia says:
напала Россия а если Россия говорит:
"That's it, we are leaving, we are leaving the borders of
"Всё мы выходим мы выходим на границы
1991 and that's it," so
девяносто первого года и всё" так
Ukraine will say, let's say, you have caused us a lot of
Украина скажет допустим вот вы нам много
harm, we are now also attacking, no, that's it,
вреда нанесли мы сейчас тоже атакуем нет
look, Russia is leaving  Russia
всё смотрите выходит Россия Россия
does just look, comes out on the border and
делает просто смотри выходит на границе
says: "Let's sign, sign an agreement
говорит: "Подписыем подписываем договор
that we will go to the borders of
что мы выходим на границы девяносто
1991 and that's it, and we have no claims against each
первого года и всё и претензий друг к
other" for example, why don't you
другу не имеем" например почему так не
do that, well,
сделаете
and why don't we have claims, say, let
ну а чего претензий не имеют скаж
's say, get rid of the common weapon, don't
допустим избавьтесь от единого оружия не
get rid of it, you are the aggressors, we attack,
избавляетесь вы агрессоры мы нападаем
why, well, everything is fine if Ukraine Oh yeah,
почему ну всё хорошо если Украина О да
Ukraine attacks Sudzha Russia hits
Украина нападает на Суджу Россия бьёт по
Kyiv then with nuclear weapons and that's it, so what's
Киеву тогда ядерным оружием и всё
good about that, well, that's it, so that
так что там хорошего-то
Ukraine doesn't attack and that's it, and well, we can strike
ну так всё чтобы Украина не напала и всё
again No, wait,
и ну так можно ещё раз ударить нет
okay, according to your logic, now we
погоди хорошо по твоей логике сейчас
can also strike with this weapon, you do
тоже можно ударить эным оружием ты типа
n't see the problem in striking with this weapon I
не видишь проблемы в ударе эным оружием
see, if Ukraine attacked Russia,
вижу вижу если б на Россию напала
it would be possible, but now Russia is the
Украина это можно было а сейчас Россия
aggressor, no one in the world will
агрессор никто не поймёт в мире
understand, you understand, okay, let's
понимаешь хорошо давай немножко
roll back a little, you named a lot, although not
откатимся ты вот назвал много хотя не
very many, okay, the advantages of rolling back borders, come on,
особо много о'кей плюсы отката границ
come on, now look at the question, yes,
вот давай давай теперь смотри вопрос да
no, wait, wait, wait, you
нет погоди погоди погоди погоди ты
said something like stopping the war, well,
высказался типа остановка войны хорошо в
what's the problem, stopping  war along the current
чём проблема остановить войну по текущей
border what is the problem eh Ukraine does not
границе в чём проблема э Украина не
agree here Ukraine does not agree you
согласна вот Украина не согласна
understand because look if they
понимаешь потому что смотри если
stop along the current border yes in
остановят по ээ текущей границе да в
Ukraine problems will start you understand
Украине начнутся проблемы всё понимаешь
no so yes so look now it turns
нет так вот да так смотри теперь
out well and social groups
получается хорошо а социальные группы
some citizens will come out
выйдут какие-то градан выйдут все
absolutely everyone will come out absolutely everyone
абсолютно все выйдут абсолютно все
will come out and the army will come out now a question for
выйдут да и армия выйдет теперь вопрос к
you look it turns out here no here not here
тебе смотри получается тут нет тут не
not a mirror because look
тут не зеркалка потому что смотри
Ukraine says if we go to the borders of
Украина говорит если выходим на границы
ninety-one we stop and
девяносто первого года останавливаемся и
Russia should say: "We go to the
Россия должна сказать: "Мы выходим на
borders of ninety-one and
границы девяносто первого года и
stop" this is a compromise you see
останавливаемся" это компромисс видишь
no no no some kind of compromise why because
нене не какой компромисс почему потому
look no if they stop No look
что смотри нет если останавли Нет смотри
if they stop they stop along the
если останав останавливается по линии
demarcation line of the modern yes it
разграничения современной да это
turns out that Russia has seized the
получается что Россия захватила
territory of Ukraine Ukraine will never
территорию Украины украина никогда на
agree to this now look it turns out
это не пойдёт теперь смотри получается
you A And because we won't go and that's it how are
вы А потому что вот не пойдём и всё как
you how are you going to how are you yes a question in the
вы как вы собираетесь как вы да вопрос
regulation a question yes look how are you going to
врегументации вопрос да смотри как вы
collect how are you going to force
собирае как вы собираетесь заставить
Ukraine to capitulate along the
Украину капитулировать по линии
demarcation line as well as
разграничения как
now as far as I know the line is
ну сейчас насколько я знаю линия
still moving in favor of Russia well
всё-таки движется в пользу России ну
let it be a meter there in short there a meter like yes per
пусть там метр короче там метр типа да в
year and that's it yes the question how are you going to
год и всё да вопрос как ты собираешься
okay then it makes sense to ask the question:
хорошо тогда имеет смысл задать вопрос:
"And how are you going to make Russia stop
"А как вы заставите Россию остановиться
and we are not going to we look we will
а мы не собираемся мы смотри мы будем
fight to the last Russian for example
воевать до последнего русского например
yes Ukraine said Zelensky said
да украина сказала Зеленский сказал
Zelensky said like we will
Зеленский сказал типа мы будем до
fight to the last Russian the question look look well to us look
последнего россиянина воевать вопрос
we are puppets of the USA
смотри смотри ну нам смотри мы
like here in short the USA
марионетки США типа тут короче нами США
controls us puppets the USA now look
управляе марионетки США тепер смотри
okay let's
хорошо давай условно давай давай
say let's say let's look again let's
допустим давай смо ещё раз смотри давай
we howl to the last Ukrainian you to the
мы воем до последнего украинца вы до
last Russian what do you need
последнего русска вам что нужно
territories or living people
территории или живые люди
and this and that so stop stop why do you need our
и то и то так стоп стоп зачем вам наши
territories
территории
well form brigades that is you support the
ну бригадятся а то есть ты поддерживаешь
seizure of the territory of Ukraine you
захват территории Украины ты
support the war against Ukraine well rather no well how
поддерживаешь войну против Украины
rather no the question well how
ну скорее нет ну как скорее нет вопрос
rather no what is unclear to you
ну как скорее нет что тебе непонятного
you supported clearly a minute ago okay why do
ты минуту назад поддерживал чётко
you need the territory of Ukraine
хорошо зачем вам территория Украины
because it is our land
потому что это наша земля
and what does that say well  and that this is our
и что это говорит ну и что вот это наша
land God gave us because God look
земля нам Бог дал потому что Бог смотри
God when he created the globe yes he
Бог когда создавал земной шарик да он
said: "This is Ukrainian" god what
сказал: "Это украин" бог какой у тебя
god do you have Perun
бог перун
Perun yes Perun when he created the globe
перун да перун когда создавал земной шар
yes he said Ukraine and then he
да он сказал Украина и тут же украша
created decorations do you think yes he created the globe so
создавал думаешь да он шар создал так
look now I'm in space
вот смотри теперь я же в космосе
sources brother I saw in space
источники брат я в космосе видел
when I was remember like I flew so
когда был помнишь типа я летал так вот
look the question that is to say God did I
смотри вопрос то есть Бога всё-таки
see Perun I saw the question yes yes I saw Perun yes look
видел Перуна видел вопрос да да перуна
I deceived you yes I fooled you
видел да смотри я тебя обманул да развёл
like
как
"to fool a Russian is in short a sacred
"развести россиянина - это короче святое
thing" said Perun now Now look the
дело" сказал Перун тепер Теперь смотри
question the question uh it turns out that you don't
вопрос вопрос ээ получается что вы не
see how you will force
видите как вы заставите
Ukraine to capitulate right well what should you capture
Украину капитулировать правильно ну что
Kiev capture Lvov
вы должны захватить Киев захватить Львов
capture Berlin how do you see your
захватить Берлин как вы видите свою
victory at the end of the war well
победу окончании войны
when Ukraine runs out of resources
ну когда Украина кончатся ресурсы
resources well how many years do you want to
ресурсы хорошо сколько лет вы хотите так
fight like this so that Ukraine runs out of resources that's what you
воевать чтобы Украина кончилась ресурсы
think I don't want at all
вот как вы считаете я нисколько не хочу
I don't want Well that's how you see look you've been howling for the
я по Ну вот как ты видишь смотри вот вы
fourth year now how much have you  And you
воете уже четвёртый год сколько вы А ты
estimate that Russia will still fight
оцениваешь ещё будет воевать Россия
so that Ukraine runs out of resources, well,
чтобы у Украины кончились ресурсы
probably in about a year and a half, and in about a year and a half,
ну года полтора наверное а года полтора
I understand, from the current trend, I understand, so
понял с текущей тенденции понял так
good, if Ukraine runs out of
хорошо если у Украины заканчивается
resources, then you can easily
ресурсы значит что вы тогда спокойно
reach Kyiv or Lvov, not along the
доходите до Киева или до Львова не не по
current border, that's what the border will be, so let's
текущей границе вот какая будет граница
stop, so wait, look,
так и остановимся так подожди смотри е
look, if Ukraine runs out of
смотри если у Украины закончились
resources, then you can move the
ресурсы то вы можете тогда двигать
border wherever you want, really, well, we
границу куда хочешь правда
can, but why, wait, I'll tell you along the
ну можем но зачем подожди я вас по
current border,
текущей границе
so again I don't understand, look, for example,
так ещё раз не понял смотри например
if you have, well, look, let's say there were
если у Да ну смотри условно вот были до
many wars before, and the borders of
этого множество войн да границы менялись
states changed, how do you think this
у государств как по-твоему это
happened, that is, either one
происходило то есть всегда либо одно
state always completely disappeared, or,
государство полностью исчезало или
after all, there were situations when both
всё-таки вот бывали ситуации когда оба
states were at war, one won, well,
государства воюет одно побеждает да ну
look, once again, a peace treaty was being conceived,
смотри ещё раз чается мирный договор
after which part of the border it,
после которого часть границы оно вот
look, Ukraine, let's do this, if
смотри вот Украина давай так если
Ukraine does not sign, under no
Украина не подписывает ни при каких
circumstances, does not sign a peace
обстоятельствах не подписывает мирный
treaty, what do you need, what do you need to do, seize
договор вам нужно что вам нужно
Kyiv, put your
захватить Киев поставить туда своего
ruler there so that he will do, for example, what will
правителя чтобы он сделает например что
Ukraine do, well, it stands along this
Украина сделает ну вот она стоит по этой
line, yes, but it does not sign  peace
линии да но не подписывает мирный
treaty
договор
so what well that is it turns out you will
ну и что ну то есть получается вы будете
forever fight brother with Japan okay we are
вечно воевать брат с Японией хорошо мы с
forever fighting with Japan now I don't I
Японией вечно воюем сейчас я вот я не Я
understand correctly that you will
правильно понимаю что вы будете воевать
forever fight with Ukraine that is if Ukraine does not
вечно с Украиной то есть если Украина не
sign mines in your understanding I
подпишет мины в твоём понимании я тебя
heard you in yours so that I can understand to
услышал в твоём чтобы мне понимать
answer your question I need to understand
ответить на твой вопрос мне нужно понять
how you relate let's say and with the relationship
как ты относишь допустим а со отношением
with Japan
с Японией у
Russia is in a state of war on I no no
России состояние войны на Я нет нет
look I didn't see Japan bombing
смотри я не видел чтобы Япония бомбила
Russia or we with them I didn't see that No the
Россили мы с ними я не видел чтобы Нет
thing is that Japan signed
дело в том что Япония подписала
the surrender of the Americans
капитуляцию американцев
I'm not asking about that and you and it came out and
я не про это спрашиваю и вы и вышло и
then came out of the war and here a completely different
вышло тогда из войны а тут совсем другой
treaty with Japan is not finished okay come on
договор с Японией не закончен хорошо
look okay let's
давай смотри ладно давай ещё раз
explain again look you stand in line and we
объясняю смотри вы стоите по линии и мы
stand in line we are not moving anywhere but
стоим по линии мы никуда не двигаемся но
we launch drones that bomb
мы запускаем беспилотники которые бомбят
Moscow Petersburg Saratov and so on well
Москву Петербург Саратов и так дальше да
and we launch missiles that bomb
ну а мы запускаем ракеты которые бомбят
Krivoy Rog for you everything that is you get A
Кривой Рог для вас всё то есть получае А
that is children
то есть детей
no, not children, well, Krivoy Rog, you specifically
нет не детей ну Кривой Рог ты специально
said Krivoy Rog, that is, children in Krivoy
сказал Кривой Рог то есть детей в Кривом
Rogush, children, well, there are no soldiers there and one
Рогушь детей ну там нет военных и одного
battle, who was killed by a missile in Krivoy Rog,
боя кого кого убила ракета в Кривом Роге
what kind of ballistic missile was that a couple of days
какая вот эта баллистическая пару дней
ago, you specifically killed children, yes,
назад ты же специально с детей убила да
children, children, you see, yes, that is, and you
детей детей видишь да то есть и ты
specifically said Krivoy Rog, yes, what are you talking
специально сказал Кривой Рог да
about, well, why did you specifically
нет о чём ты ну а почему ты именно
say Krivoy Rog there and not Kyiv, for example,
сказал Кривой Рог там а не Киев например
well, an example, a beautiful name of the city, brother, yeah, I
ну пример красивое название города брат
got it, it’s interesting, but in Kiev, children were not
ага понял интересно а в Киеве детей не
killed, no, I’m against it, and in Kyiv, they
убивало не не мне против и в Киеве
killed in the hospital, Akhmad too, yes, that
убивали в больнице Ахмад тоже да ну то
is, if you had said Kiev, well, where did they
есть если бы сказал в Киев хорошо а где
not kill children, the city was
не убивал детей город всюду Россия
everywhere, Russia killed children,
убивала детей всюду Россия убивала дете
literally, Wait, wait, that is,
буквально Погоди погоди то есть
literally any city, children were killed, so what are
буквально любой город детей убивали так
you complaining about, I’ll explain it in a new
а что ты какие претензии повому
way, because Yes, this is fresh
розови объясню потому что Да это свежая
news and you specifically said it because
новость и ты специально её сказал потому
you support the killing of these children,
что ты поддерживаешь убийство этих детей
okay, then look, you’re hitting, you’re hitting
ладно дальше смотри вы бьёте вы бьёте
Ukraine with missiles, Ukraine is bombing your
ракетами по Украине украина бомбит ваши
cities with drones, there are American ones
города дронами там американскими
British and so on yes it turns out that the
британскими и так дальше да получается у
bombing of your territory will never
вас бомбёжка вашей территории никогда не
stop well
остановится
according to your logic I never understood that is
ну по твоей логике никогда понял то есть
you want how it is quite pointless and
вы хотите ка это довольно бессмысленно и
it will end why it is pointless well like it is
это закончится почему бессмысленно
unprofitable in general for Well look come on let's
ну типа невыгодно в целом для Ну смотри
look if Russia
давай давай так смотри если Россия
stops at the demarcation line and does
останавливается по линии разграничения и
not advance on Kyiv kudos to Kiev to
не наступает на Киев почет Киеву
launch drones further on Moscow
запускать дальше по Москве дроны
well many factors can decide not to
ну множество факторов могут решать не
interfere there for example for example I don't know there the
мешать там например например не знаю там
orange man will say: "Don't launch
оранжевый человек скажет: "Не запускаете
otherwise we will cut your subsidies" well and for
иначе мы вам субсидии урежем" ну а
example this is Ukraine's nuclear weapons yes
например это ядерным оружием Украины да
what prevented Ukraine from keeping its nuclear weapons for
что мешало Украине оставить ярное оружие
itself what do you think again look at the question
себе как думаешь ещё раз смотри вопрос
yes Ukraine yes for example orange the orange
да Украина да например оранже оранжевый
man says: "We are there for you subsidies" and the
человек говорит: "Мы там вам субсидии" а
Nazis yes in Ukraine all sorts of Right
нацисты да в Украине всякие Правый
Sector they will bomb Moscow and not
сектор они будут бомбить Москву и не
listen to Zelensky I don't listen to
слушать Зеленски я не не слушаю
propaganda no need this nonsense no you are a
пропаганду не надо вот это вот глупости
victim of propaganda or you were like
нет ты ты жертва пропаганды либо ты от
this from birth
рождения такой
and in what I am a victim of propaganda
а в чём я жертва пропаганды
yes in the fact that you support the murder of people in
да в том что поддержишь убийство людей в
Ukraine and I  don't take you i support
Украине и я тебя не брать поддерживаю
killing people i just think that war
убийство людей просто я считаю что война
by definition is killing people
по определению - это убийство людей
consider that during
считать что во время
war your soldiers are knights who
войны твои солдаты рыцари которые мирных
don't kill civilians come on tell me who
людей не убивают давай расскажи кто
okay who are you come on tell me who is to
хорошо кто ты давай так скажи кто кто
blame for Russia attacking
виноват в том что Россия напала на
Ukraine take wait let me ask you a question come on do you think
Украину брать погоди дай тебе вопрос
what do you think
задам давай ты считаешь как думаешь
Ukrainian soldiers have ever killed
украинские солдаты когда-нибудь убивали
civilians no well what do you
Мирняк нет
think who is brainwashed me or you that is do
ну как думаешь кто промыты я или ты то
you think during war your
есть ты считаешь во время войны твоя
side never killed civilians my
сторона ни разу мирняк не убивала моя
country is defending itself from Russian
страна защищается от российского
aggressor yes yes and that's not what i'm
агрессора да да и что я не про это
asking and that yes because you Yes
спрашиваю и что да потому что вы Да
support killing people in Ukraine
поддерживаете убийство людей в Украине
yes yes and we are defending ourselves we are hitting military
да да а мы защищаемся мы бьём по военным
targets and you are hitting playgrounds
объектам а вы бьёте по детским площадкам
now look at the question for you yes it
теперь смотри вопрос к тебе да
turns out that you will forever tolerate
получается что вы будете вечно терпеть
shelling of your territory this will never
обстрелы своей территории это никогда не
end a new topic this is a pretty
закончится новую тему это довольно
stupid topic come on okay come on come on come on come on a
глупая тема давай хорошо давай давай
new one come on a new one how come get a
давай давай новую давай новую тему как
new one how did it happen that how did it
так получи новень так как как получилось
happen that  140 million Russians
что как получилось что 140 млн россиян
became like this, yes, they did
стали такими
n’t become like this, why were they, I understand, let’s do it like
да не стали почему а были понял
this,
давай вот так
cynical, cynical, yes, and we will be there,
циничные циничные да а мы будем там
Krivoy Rog, yes, he says it on purpose, yes,
Кривой Рог да он специально говорит да
they specifically want to draw you out on
они специально хотят вас вытянуть на
emotions, yes, they specifically, three or three
эмоции да они специально тут три или 3
days ago, uh, there
дня назад ээ
were these flights, yes, and she sits there, grinning,
были эти прилёты да и она сидит лыбится
saying: “And we will send a missile to Krivoy Rog,”
это говорит: "А мы ракету в Кривой Рог"
yes, he says it so peacefully, for
да намирность он прямо так говорит для
him, the murder of peaceful people, children, in
него убийство мирных людей детей в
huge numbers, is
огромном количестве это
funny, because he supports Russia,
смешно потому что он поддерживает Россию
because that’s all, these, you
потому что вот это это все вот эти
see, good Russians, who I am against
видите хорошие русские которые я против
war, but I support my country,
войны но я поддерживаю свою страну
because that’s all, I am against war, but
потому что и всё я против войны но и
after that, their
после
real
ночинается ихняя вот эта реальная
hell will appear, which they have, which is sitting in
ад который у них сидит в
Therefore, therefore, no, never
Поэтому поэтому не это не когда
believe in good people, yes, who
не верьте в хороших да которые вам
tell you sweet speeches, like, subscribe,
рассказывают сладкие речи лайк подписка
comment, subscribe to my Telegram right
комент подпишись на ми Telegram прямо
now, that’s it, and the priest,
зараз ось він а попик
that’s very important, YouTube is driving
це дуже і дуже важливо youtube заганяє
us through jail cells into a shadow ban  And even a
нас через каргерки в тіньовий бан і дуже
lot of videos are not shown to people,
багато відео не показуется людям вчасно
information about the stream is not shown at all times,
не показуется інформація про стрими тому
so that we have a small prompt connection to
для того щоб ми мали оперативный зв'язок
subscribe right away, and the pop up there in the
підпишиться прямо зараз а попик там в
telegram is still the same and
телеграмі окмдео ще теж є цікава и
useful information and we are to blame  We
корисна інформація и мы повинні з вами
will have a permanent operational connection with you, and we will
тримати постійний оперативный зв'язок
show you about this
незалежно від того чи покаже вам про цей
YouTube, glory to Ukraine, subscribe
YouTube слава Україні підпишись